# AKPAN, VICTORIA DAVID

# Front-end Web Developer

Phone: +2347087040050 | Email: veedahv55@gmail.com | GitHub: github.com/veedahv | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/victoria-akpan | Twitter: https://twitter.com/veedahv | Website: veedahv.me

#### **PROFILE**

I am a front-end web developer who specializes in creating fast and accessible websites. I reproduce replicas of designs using appropriate front-end technologies. I have experience working with and possess good knowledge of the following:

SKILLS - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VueJS, Bootstrap, git

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Front-End Intern - Ustacky

December 2020 - September 2021

- I implemented designs using web technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VueJs, Bootstrap.
- I mentored and helped students where they need help.

## Code Reviewer - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

• I review students' code and provide valuable feedback and advice.

#### Web Developer – Codekago

November 2021 - till date

I implement designs using web technologies.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Front-End Micro-degree - Ustacky

December 2020 - March 2021

• I implemented an e-commerce website design integrated with Paystack test payment method.

### Web Development - The Roothub

August - October 2020

- Created a shopping list app.
- Created a weather app.
- Created an e-commerce dashboard for an online store.

#### Front-End Development - FrontEndFoxes

April - June 2021

- Built a Bank App.
- Built a Typing Game.
- Built a Pet App.

• Built a Browser Extension.

### **Computer Engineering –** University of Uyo

September 2017 - Till date

• Built a simple airline booking platform

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

# **Front-End Developer –** GiveCampMemphis

February 2021

• I helped rebuild the mobile view of The Women Advocacy Center Site.

# Core Team Member – GDSC Uniuyo

September 2021 - Till date

• I organize GDSC Uniuyo events along with my co-lead (events management) and other core team members.

#### **AWARDS**

• Finalist at the Enye hackathon(2020)